export default {
  id: 'low_1006_3_1b',
  name: '상용한자(3학년-1/한자찾기)',
  data: [
    { question: '독:そ(る)、そ(らす)/음:はん、ほん、たん', answer: ['反'] },
    { question: '독:대할/음:たい、つい', answer: ['対(對)'] },
    { question: '독:かる(い)、かろ(やか)/음:けい', answer: ['軽(輕)'] },
    { question: '독:え、おも(い)、かさ(ねる)、かさ(なる)/음:じゅう、ちょう', answer: ['重'] },
    { question: '독:さむ(い)/음:かん', answer: ['寒'] },
    { question: '독:あつ(い)/음:しょ', answer: ['暑(暑)'] },
    { question: '독:のぼ(る)/음:とう、と', answer: ['登'] },
    { question: '독:お(ちる)、お(とす)/음:らく', answer: ['落'] },
    { question: '독:かみ、かん、こう/음:しん、じん', answer: ['神(神)'] },
    { question: '독:みや/음:きゅう、ぐう、く', answer: ['宮'] },
    { question: '독:うつ(す)、うつ(る)/음:しゃ', answer: ['写(寫)'] },
    { question: '독:ま/음:しん', answer: ['真(眞)'] },
    { question: '독:たび/음:りょ', answer: ['旅(旅)'] },
    { question: '독:やかた/음:かん', answer: ['館(館)'] },
    { question: '독:기약할/음:き、ご', answer: ['期'] },
    { question: '독:ま(つ)/음:たい', answer: ['待'] },
    { question: '독:き(える)、け(す)/음:しょう', answer: ['消(消)'] },
    { question: '독:いき/음:そく', answer: ['息'] },
    { question: '독:お(わる)、お(える)/음:しゅう', answer: ['終'] },
    { question: '독:き(る)、き(せる)、つ(く)、つ(ける)/음:ちゃく、じゃく', answer: ['着'] },
    { question: '독:역/음:えき', answer: ['駅(驛)'] },
    { question: '독:はじ(まる)、はじ(める)/음:し', answer: ['始'] },
    { question: '독:필/음:はつ、ほつ', answer: ['発(發)'] },
    { question: '독:や(む)、やまい/음:びょう、へい', answer: ['病'] },
    { question: '독:집/음:いん', answer: ['院'] },
    { question: '독:なが(れる)、なが(す)/음:りゅう、る', answer: ['流'] },
    { question: '독:ち/음:けつ', answer: ['血'] },
    { question: '독:의원/음:い', answer: ['医(醫)'] },
    { question: '독:もの/음:しゃ', answer: ['者(者)'] },
    { question: '독:くすり/음:やく', answer: ['薬(藥)'] },
    { question: '독:판/음:きょく', answer: ['局'] },
    { question: '독:이름/음:ごう', answer: ['号(號)'] },
    { question: '독:まった(く)、すべ(て)/음:ぜん', answer: ['全(全)'] },
    { question: '독:み/음:しん', answer: ['身'] },
    { question: '독:あそ(ぶ)/음:ゆう、ゆ', answer: ['遊(遊)'] },
    { question: '독:およ(ぐ)/음:えい', answer: ['泳'] },
    { question: '독:いそ(ぐ)/음:きゅう', answer: ['急'] },
    { question: '독:はや(い)、はや(める)、はや(まる)、すみ(やか)/음:そく', answer: ['速(速)'] },
    { question: '독:やす(い)/음:あん', answer: ['安'] },
    { question: '독:う(つ)/음:だ', answer: ['打'] },
    { question: '독:ね(る)/음:れん', answer: ['練(練)'] },
    { question: '독:なら(う)/음:しゅう', answer: ['習(習)'] },
    { question: '독:か(つ)、まさ(る)/음:しょう', answer: ['勝'] },
    { question: '독:ま(ける)、ま(かす)、お(う)/음:ふ', answer: ['負'] },
    { question: '독:な(げる)/음:とう', answer: ['投'] },
    { question: '독:たま/음:きゅう', answer: ['球'] },
    { question: '독:さいわ(い)、さち、しあわ(せ)/음:こう', answer: ['幸'] },
    { question: '독:복/음:ふく', answer: ['福(福)'] },
    { question: '독:느낄/음:かん', answer: ['感'] },
    { question: '독:うご(く)、うご(かす)/음:どう', answer: ['動'] },
    { question: '독:벌일/음:れつ', answer: ['列'] },
    { question: '독:しま/음:とう', answer: ['島'] },
    { question: '독:う(ける)、う(かる)/음:じゅ', answer: ['受'] },
    { question: '독:と(る)/음:しゅ', answer: ['取'] },
    { question: '독:もの/음:ぶつ、もつ', answer: ['物'] },
    { question: '독:しな/음:ひん', answer: ['品'] },
    { question: '독:くば(る)/음:はい', answer: ['配'] },
    { question: '독:おく(る)/음:そう', answer: ['送(送)'] },
    { question: '독:あきな(う)/음:しょう', answer: ['商'] },
    { question: '독:わざ/음:ぎょう、ごう', answer: ['業'] },
    { question: '독:쇠/음:てつ', answer: ['鉄(鐵)'] },
    { question: '독:はし/음:きょう', answer: ['橋'] },
    { question: '독:の(る)、の(せる)/음:じょう', answer: ['乗'] },
    { question: '독:손님/음:きゃく、かく', answer: ['客'] },
    { question: '독:す(む)、す(まう)/음:じゅう', answer: ['住'] },
    { question: '독:ところ/음:しょ', answer: ['所'] },
    { question: '독:つか(える)/음:し', answer: ['仕'] },
    { question: '독:こと/음:じ、ず', answer: ['事'] },
    { question: '독:すす(む)、すす(める)/음:しん', answer: ['進(進)'] },
    { question: '독:じ/음:ろ', answer: ['路'] },
    { question: '독:ころ(がる)、ころ(げる)、ころ(がす)、ころ(ぶ)/음:てん', answer: ['転(轉)'] },
    { question: '독:む(く)、む(かう)、む(ける)、む(こう)/음:こう', answer: ['向'] },
    { question: '독:と(ぐ)/음:けん', answer: ['研(硏)'] },
    { question: '독:きわ(める)/음:きゅう', answer: ['究'] },
    { question: '독:あい/음:そう、しょう', answer: ['相'] },
    { question: '독:말씀/음:だん', answer: ['談'] },
    { question: '독:やど、やど(る)、やど(す)/음:しゅく', answer: ['宿'] },
    { question: '독:제목/음:だい', answer: ['題'] },
    { question: '독:시/음:し', answer: ['詩'] },
    { question: '독:あつ(まる)、あつ(める)、つど(う)/음:しゅう', answer: ['集'] },
    { question: '독:뜻/음:い', answer: ['意'] },
    { question: '독:あじ、あじ(わう)/음:み', answer: ['味'] },
    { question: '독:ゆだ(ねる)/음:い', answer: ['委'] },
    { question: '독:인원/음:いん', answer: ['員'] },
    { question: '독:きみ/음:くん', answer: ['君'] },
    { question: '독:ぬし、おも/음:しゅ、す', answer: ['主'] },
    { question: '독:たい(ら)、ひら/음:へい、びょう', answer: ['平(平)'] },
    { question: '독:ひと(しい)/음:とう', answer: ['等'] },
    { question: '독:お(う)/음:つい', answer: ['追(追)'] },
    { question: '독:はな(す)、はな(つ)、はな(れる)、ほう(る)/음:ほう', answer: ['放'] },
    { question: '독:예도/음:れい、らい', answer: ['礼(禮)'] },
    { question: '독:법/음:しき', answer: ['式'] },
    { question: '독:つか(う)/음:し', answer: ['使'] },
    { question: '독:いのち/음:めい、みょう', answer: ['命'] },
    { question: '독:わる(い)/음:あく、お', answer: ['悪(惡)'] },
    { question: '독:ふで/음:ひつ', answer: ['筆'] },
    { question: '독:の(む)/음:いん', answer: ['飲(飮)'] },
    { question: '독:さけ、さか/음:しゅ', answer: ['酒'] },
    { question: '독:떼/음:ぶ', answer: ['部'] },
    { question: '독:や/음:おく', answer: ['屋'] }
  ]
}
